# Bhavesh Chalke

LEVEL DESIGNER / GAME DESIGNER GAME DEVELOPER

9702818569

bchalke4513@gmail.com

Mumbai 400037

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a Level Designer, have some experience in Game Development, 3D Modelling and Software Development. Quality delivery is my all time priority and I always put extreme level of attention to details. I am well versed with relevant technologies.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2020-Present

## Level Designer

## Tecknotrove Systems

Primary role is to create game scenario based on 3D game environment which initiates the player into the world of the game

## 2019-2020

## Game Designer

## rthetapi.com

Primary role was to create game environment for educational, exercise, or experimental purposes.

#### 2017-2019

## Freelancing

Logo/Graphic Design, Web Development 3D Modelling.

# **EDUCATION**

2019

GRA

# Bachelor of Engineering (IT)

Vidyalankar Institute of Technology

Mumbai University CGPA - 7.2

2016

DIPLOM

## Information Technology

Vidyalankar Polytechnic

Maharashtra State Board of Technical Education

Score - 76.66%

2013

SSC

#### General

Score - 76.91%

Shri Bansidhar Aggarwal Model School

Maharashtra State Board

## SKILLS

Unity 3D

Blender

Adobe Photoshop

Substance Painter

**Xnormal** 

Photogrammetry

C#, Java, Shader Programming

Hardware

Wondershare Filmora

Adobe Illustrator

## INTERESTS







Activity C

Gaming Design